24, about the invocation of our Maryland Reverend of All Saints,
Bishop of Church, and his name is David.
Let us pray.
Holy God, we thank you for gathering us together for this meeting.
In this busy time, give us calm, give us peace.
Help us to set aside the troubles of the day that we carried with us to this place.
So we can be present to one another and to you.
We seek your blessing as we share ideas, progress, and accomplishments,
and go about doing the work you've called us to do.
You've charged us with being your hands and feet here on earth
for seeing opportunities in many circumstances, both big and small.
And so please reveal to us through our discussion and decisions
what you would have us do.
If we have differences, help us to resolve those in a manner that leaves everyone's dignity
in place, and with a solution that brings light into our community.
Help us to have the strength to carry out your mission of love, justice, peace, and gratitude in our community.
This day and always.
We ask this through your Son, our Savior, Jesus Christ.
Amen.
Congratulations to the flag of the United States of America, and to the Republic for which
it stands.
One nation, another nation, another nation, and a nation for which we can be in justice tomorrow.
Four above again, but let's go to the first of all, Francis, five claims list, Mr. Trooper.
Second.
Please step.
Hi.
Thank you.
Six minutes from the November 18th, 2024 regular meeting.
Who's to approve?
E step.
Double.
Hi.
Jones.
Tax cards.
Hi.
Seven.
Measurement.
Number 25, dash 13.
Receiving your spending money from sale and well one scrap metal to assist with unforeseen
repairs.
Jill.
This is unforeseen repairs for a well one, they're wanting to use that scrap money that they
got for that.
The repairs more than that.
I know they moved to 15,000 from another account, so it's pretty substantial on the expense.
Joe, I, Barnes, I, E-step, Parker.
Hi.
Hey, annual contractor rule as needed, aggregate rock, C-23-59, with Kim Stone, Brian.
Trustees and Mayor, we would like to renew this in your packet or the amendment signed by
the annual contractor, and it's Kim Stone, it's the only one that we have to do the aggregate
rock, and we recommend the adendum be approved and signed.
This one we have this, and it has been signed now.
Let's try and prove.
Hi.
Joe, I, Barnes, I, Parker.
Not annual contractor, at all, for concrete, sand, supply, C-23-60, and scoggy sand.
And this one's the same way we want to get the adendum to be approved and signed, and this
is another one that's Muscogee sand, and it's the only one that we have for this project.
Motion approved.
That's it.
So, cool.
Hi.
Thanks.
I, Barnes, I, E-step.
Hi.
Parker.
Hey, then, annual contractor rule as needed, concrete material, C-23-61, with an annual concrete.
An annual concrete will be our only concrete material supplier.
They're, we talked about pricing and everything.
All of these companies are staying at the same pricing.
So, along with an annual, and we recommend the adendum be approved and signed, we need to
approve.
Motion approved.
Hi.
Joe, I, E-step.
So, cool.
Hi.
Parker.
13.
Trustee, community announcements.
14.
This meeting will be continued from Cal Jvert, Recre, and the staff room for the purpose of
executive session.
That's the completion of agenda item number 20 of the regga mate of the Monocity Council.